export const PROBLEM_OF_MONTH_2015 = [
  {
    month: "January",
    year: 2015,
    question: "1412q.pdf",
    solution: "1501a.pdf",
    solvers: [
      { name: "Toshihiro Shimizu", affiliation: "Kawasaki, Japan" },
      { name: "William Wu Cheng Yuan", affiliation: "Singapore" },
      { name: "Julian Al-Zukaimi", affiliation: "Higher Institue for Applied Science & Technology, Syria" },
      { name: "Harald Bogeholz", affiliation: "c t Computer magazine, Germany" },
      { name: "Tomas Jurik", affiliation: "Kosice, Slovakia" },
      { name: "Erdem Ünal", affiliation: "Finansbank, İstanbul" },
      { name: "Bojan Basic", affiliation: "Novi Sad, Serbia" },
      { name: "Mehmet Ali Yıldırım", affiliation: "Fatih Koleji, İstanbul" }
    ]
  },
  {
    month: "February",
    year: 2015,
    question: "1501q.pdf",
    solution: "1502a.pdf",
    solvers: [
      { name: "Toshihiro Shimizu", affiliation: "Kawasaki, Japan" },
      { name: "Albert Stadler", affiliation: "Herrliberg, Switzerland" },
      { name: "Harald Bogeholz", affiliation: "c t Computer magazine, Germany" },
      { name: "Kipp Johnson", affiliation: "Valley Catholic School, Beaverton, Oregon, USA" },
      { name: "Tomas Jurik", affiliation: "Kosice, Slovakia" },
      { name: "William Wu Cheng Yuan", affiliation: "Singapore" },
      { name: "Melissa Bucknor", affiliation: "London, U.K." },
      { name: "Darko Ninkovic", affiliation: "School of Electrical Engineering, Belgrade, Serbia" },
      { name: "Yasuo Yamane", affiliation: "Machida, Japan" },
      { name: "Julian Al-Zukaimi", affiliation: "Higher Institute for Applied Science & Technology, Syria" },
      { name: "Ruben Victor Cohen", affiliation: "Argentina" },
      { name: "Eskil Jarlskog", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" },
      { name: "Bojan Basic", affiliation: "Novi Sad, Serbia" },
      { name: "Erdem Ünal", affiliation: "Finansbank, İstanbul" },
      { name: "Mustafa Turgut", affiliation: "Selçuk, İzmir" },
      { name: "Arthur Vause", affiliation: "Preston, Lancashire, U.K." },
      { name: "İbrahim Emre Kıvanççı", affiliation: "Bornova Anadolu Lisesi, İzmir" },
      { name: "Borja Elizalde Masia", affiliation: "Barcelona, Spain" }
    ]
  },
  {
    month: "March",
    year: 2015,
    question: "1502q.pdf",
    solution: "1503a.pdf",
    solvers: [
      { name: "Toshihiro Shimizu", affiliation: "Kawasaki, Japan" },
      { name: "Yasuo Yamane", affiliation: "Machida, Japan" },
      { name: "William Wu Cheng Yuan", affiliation: "Singapore" },
      { name: "Julian Al-Zukaimi", affiliation: "Higher Institue for Applied Science & Technology, Syria" },
      { name: "Tomas Jurik", affiliation: "Kosice, Slovakia" },
      { name: "Bojan Basic", affiliation: "Novi Sad, Serbia" }
    ]
  },
  {
    month: "April",
    year: 2015,
    question: "1503q.pdf",
    solution: "1504a.pdf",
    solvers: [
      { name: "Toshihiro Shimizu", affiliation: "Kawasaki, Japan" },
      { name: "William Wu Cheng Yuan", affiliation: "Singapore" },
      { name: "Tomas Jurik", affiliation: "Kosice, Slovakia" },
      { name: "Ramazan Karaşahin", affiliation: "TCMB, Ankara" }
    ]
  },
  {
    month: "May",
    year: 2015,
    question: "1504q.pdf",
    solution: "1505a.pdf",
    solvers: [
      { name: "Toshihiro Shimizu", affiliation: "Kawasaki, Japan" },
      { name: "Ramazan Karaşahin", affiliation: "TCMB, Ankara" },
      { name: "Tomas Jurik", affiliation: "Kosice, Slovakia" },
      { name: "Yasuo Yamane", affiliation: "Machida, Japan" },
      { name: "Arthur Vause", affiliation: "Preston, Lancashire, U.K." }
    ]
  },
  {
    month: "June",
    year: 2015,
    question: "1505q.pdf",
    solution: "1506a.pdf",
    solvers: [
      { name: "Toshihiro Shimizu", affiliation: "Kawasaki, Japan" },
      { name: "Vedat Deveci", affiliation: "DMI, İstanbul" },
      { name: "Albert Stadler", affiliation: "Herrliberg, Switzerland" },
      { name: "Arthur Vause", affiliation: "Preston, Lancashire, U.K." },
      { name: "Ramazan Karaşahin", affiliation: "TCMB, Ankara" },
      { name: "Tomas Jurik", affiliation: "Kosice, Slovakia" },
      { name: "Yasuo Yamane", affiliation: "Machida, Japan" }
    ]
  },
  {
    month: "July-August",
    year: 2015,
    question: "1506q.pdf",
    solution: "1507a.pdf",
    solvers: [
      { name: "Toshihiro Shimizu", affiliation: "Kawasaki, Japan" },
      { name: "Ramazan Karaşahin", affiliation: "TCMB, Ankara" },
      { name: "Tomas Jurik", affiliation: "Kosice, Slovakia" },
      { name: "Luis Rivera", affiliation: "Universidad Peruana de Ciencias Aplicadas, Lima, Peru" },
      { name: "Halil Özkan", affiliation: "Özel Servergazi Ortaokulu, Denizli" }
    ]
  },
  {
    month: "September",
    year: 2015,
    question: "1507q.pdf",
    solution: "1509a.pdf",
    solvers: [
      { name: "Toshihiro Shimizu", affiliation: "Kawasaki, Japan" },
      { name: "Tomas Jurik", affiliation: "Kosice, Slovakia" },
      { name: "Ozan Kaymak", affiliation: "Özel Servergazi Fen Lisesi, Denizli" },
      { name: "Arthur Vause", affiliation: "Preston, Lancashire, U.K." },
      { name: "Ramazan Karaşahin", affiliation: "TCMB, Ankara" },
      { name: "Nawal Kishor Mishra", affiliation: "Hyderabad, India" },
      { name: "Hakan Summakoğlu", affiliation: "Antakya, Hatay" },
      { name: "Luis Rivera", affiliation: "Universidad Peruana de Ciencias Aplicadas, Lima, Peru" }
    ]
  },
  {
    month: "October",
    year: 2015,
    question: "1509q.pdf",
    solution: "1510a.pdf",
    solvers: [
      { name: "Toshihiro Shimizu", affiliation: "Kawasaki, Japan" },
      { name: "Halil Özkan", affiliation: "Özel Servergazi Fen Lisesi, Denizli" },
      { name: "Vedat Deveci", affiliation: "DMO, İstanbul" },
      { name: "Tomas Jurik", affiliation: "Kosice, Slovakia" },
      { name: "Magnus Jakobsson", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" },
      { name: "Gruian Cornel", affiliation: "Cluj-Napoca, Romania" },
      { name: "Alperen Şirin", affiliation: "University of Rochester, USA" },
      { name: "Albert Stadler", affiliation: "Herrliberg, Switzerland" }
    ]
  },
  {
    month: "November",
    year: 2015,
    question: "1510q.pdf",
    solution: "1511a.pdf",
    solvers: [
      { name: "Toshihiro Shimizu", affiliation: "Kawasaki, Japan" },
      { name: "Tomas Jurik", affiliation: "Kosice, Slovakia" },
      { name: "Ata Deniz Aydın", affiliation: "Bilkent University" },
      { name: "Arthur Vause", affiliation: "Preston, Lancashire, U.K." },
      { name: "Gruian Cornel", affiliation: "Cluj-Napoca, Romania" },
      { name: "Oğuz Can Duran", affiliation: "Necip Fazıl Kısakürek Fen Lisesi, Ankara" },
      { name: "Wong Chi Fung", affiliation: "Hong Kong" },
      { name: "Mouad Faik", affiliation: "Montreal, Canada" },
      { name: "Andreas Stiller", affiliation: "c t Computer Magazin, Hannover, Germany" },
      { name: "Hasan Zubeyr Demir", affiliation: "Özel Ankara Çağlayan Fen Lisesi, Ankara" }
    ]
  },
  {
    month: "December",
    year: 2015,
    question: "1511q.pdf",
    solution: "1512a.pdf",
    solvers: [
      { name: "Toshihiro Shimizu", affiliation: "Kawasaki, Japan" },
      { name: "Tomas Jurik", affiliation: "Kosice, Slovakia" },
      { name: "Jose Hernandez-Santiago", affiliation: "Centro de Ciencias Matematicas UNAM, Morelia, Mexico" },
      { name: "Daniel Lopez-Aguayo", affiliation: "Centro de Ciencias Matematicas UNAM, Morelia, Mexico" },
      { name: "Romain Montagne", affiliation: "Montreal, Canada" },
      { name: "Hasan Zubeyr Demir", affiliation: "Özel Ankara Çağlayan Fen Lisesi, Ankara" },
      { name: "Gruian Cornel", affiliation: "Cluj-Napoca, Romania" },
      { name: "Mahmut Sait Okyay", affiliation: "UNIST, South Korea" },
      { name: "Harald Bögeholz", affiliation: "c't Computer Magazine, Germany" }
    ]
  }
];
